French Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 19th – 20th century (18 photographs) (Box 18)
  - T (16 photographs) (Box 202)
    - Troyon, Constant, 1810-1865 (14 photographs) (Box 205)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (41 photographs) (Box 205)
      - The Hague (7 photographs) (Box 206)
      - New York (5 photographs) (Box 206)
      - Paris (11 photographs) (Box 206)
      - Washington (5 photographs) (Box 206)
    - Trutat, Felix, 1824-1848 (9 photographs) (Box 206)
    - Utrillo, Maurice, 1883-1955 (39 photographs) (Box 206)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (15 photographs) (Box 206)
      - New York (9 photographs) (Box 207)
      - Paris (15 photographs) (Box 207)
  - V (36 photographs) (Box 207)
    - Valadon, Suzanne, 1865-1938 (14 photographs) (Box 207)
    - Valenciennes, Pierre Henri, 1750-1819 (14 photographs) (Box 207)
    - Valentin de Boulogne, 1591-1632 (5 photographs) (Box 207)
    - Valtat, Louis, 1869-1952 (13 photographs) (Box 207)
    - Van Marke, Emile, 1827-1890 (3 photographs) (Box 208)
    - Vasarely, Victor, 1906 or 1908-1997 (19 photographs) (Box 208)
    - Vernet, Joseph, 1714-1789 (7 photographs) (Box 208)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (39 photographs) (Box 208)
      - London (6 photographs) (Box 208)
      - Paris (15 photographs) (Box 208)
    - Vernet, Charles, 1821-1900 (6 photographs) (Box 208)
    - Vernet, EJ Horace, 1789-1863 (34 photographs) (Box 209)
    - London (11 photographs) (Box 209)
    - Vibert, Jehan Georges, 1840-1902 (6 photographs) (Box 209)
    - Vien, Joseph-Marie (6 photographs) (Box 209)
    - Vigee-Lebrun, Elisabeth L, 1755-1842 (38 photographs) (Box 209)
      - London (4 photographs) (Box 209)
      - New York (5 photographs) (Box 210)
      - Paris (9 photographs) (Box 210)
      - Versailles (7 photographs) (Box 210)
      - Washington (5 photographs) (Box 210)
    - Vignal, Pierre, 1855-1925 (26 photographs) (Box 210)
    - Villon, Jacques, 1875-1963 (Box 210)
      - Drawings (11 photographs) (Box 210)
      - Paintings (38 photographs) (Box 210)
      - Paintings II (Box 211)
    - Vincent, François André, 1746-1816 (10 photographs) (Box 211)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 1876-1958 (44 photographs) (Box 211)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (28 photographs) (Box 211)
      - Paris (10 photographs) (Box 212)
    - Vollon, Antoine, 1833-1900 (9 photographs) (Box 212)
    - Vouet, Simon, 1590-1649 (31 photographs) (Box 212)
      - Paris (12 photographs) (Box 212)
      - Rome (4 photographs) (Box 212)
    - Vuillard, Jean-Edouard, 1868-1940 (Box 212)
      - Drawings (7 photographs) (Box 212)
      - Paintings (43 photographs) (Box 213)
        - Private Collections (30 photographs) (Box 213)
          - Miscellaneous Cities (41 photographs) (Box 213)
          - New York (28 photographs) (Box 214)
          - Paris (26 photographs) (Box 214)
          - Washington (22 photographs) (Box 214)
  - W-Z (8 photographs) (Box 214)
  - Watelet, Louis E, 1780-1866 (6 photographs) (Box 214)
  - Watteau, Jean A, 1684-1721 (Box 215)
    - Drawings (16 photographs) (Box 215)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (26 photographs) (Box 215)
      - London (12 photographs) (Box 215)
      - New York (7 photographs) (Box 215)
      - Paris (16 photographs) (Box 215)
    - Paintings (11 photographs) (Box 215)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (31 photographs) (Box 216)
      - Berlin (14 photographs) (Box 216)
      - London (30 photographs) (Box 216)
      - New York (3 photographs) (Box 216)
      - Paris (24 photographs) (Box 217)
      - Washington (10 photographs) (Box 217)
  - Zao Wou-Ki, 1921- (4 photographs) (Box 217)
  - Ziem, Felix, 1821-1911 (11 photographs) (Box 217)